Her identity was a mystery to everyone. Even her.
Girl in the Picture is a documentary film directed by Skye Borgman.
A young mother’s mysterious death and her son’s subsequent kidnapping blow open a decades-long mystery
about the woman’s true identity, and the murderous federal fugitive at the center of it all.
Cheryl, played by Natalie De Vincentiis.
Joe Fitzpatrick, played by Mark Chinnery.
Heather, played by Sarah French.
Sharon, played by Dana Mackin.
Jenny, played by Meg Schimelpfenig.
Floyd, played by Robert Christopher Smith.
Girl in the Picture is an American Netflix original
documentary film directed by Skye Borgman.
It is based on the books A Beautiful Child and Finding Sharon by
Matt Birkbeck, who also served as executive producer.
The film was released on July 6, 2022.
The film explores themes of child abuse, oklahoma, based on true story,
psychological abuse, united states of america (usa).
The tone is mind_bending.